Welcome to office hours.
Today is actually our last office hours.
It's so good to see so many of you here
today.
Our most recent sessions covered
execution systems and marked a change in
how we think about and run prompts,
giving you the chance to engage in prompt
design yourself.
Again, this is our last office hours, so don't
feel like you have to limit yourself to our
most recent sessions with your questions.
We can discuss any insights or tensions and
talk broadly about the program and future
of AI enablement more broadly.
If anyone wants to jump in, feel free.
though this is the last office hours, there
are sessions a little bit more frequently,
Fridays and Mondays, so we'll also have
Q&A there, too.
All right, nobody's brave, huh?
Well, thanks for being here once again.
And I'll just maybe get the conversation
started a little bit with my current
engagements that are happening in the
world of brain up, dealing with employees,
trying to understand what people are doing
and why, and discovering that's a whole
can of worms all by itself.
And Hayden, I just thought I would invite
you to speak to this a little bit further in
terms of You know, it's occurring to me
that I kind of want to hand out forms or
have a web form and invite the players to
answer some questions ahead of time.
And you may have gone down that path
already to kind of get things started.
So the approach that I've taken is, so in the
Teams program, basically we have the first
three sessions are fairly similar, like
teaching kind of the foundations.
right, of process and value drivers, et
cetera, and having them kind of create
things.
But I had mentioned this before, but
basically the first thing you do is help them
create a role master prompt that helps
them understand their role better.
And so very similar idea from the company
master prompt, you start small and you
add to it and add to it.
And that culminates in a session with a
prompt for the Clarity Board.
And the Clarity Board does a lot of different
things.
So first of all, it surfaces, for a lot of people,
things that they've never even done before
in their role because of ineffective
delegation usually.
So for example, and I'm not, everyone I'm
sure has in some way is ineffective in
delegating.
Delegating is hard.
So in some cases that's like, they're
actually writing and issuing their own KPIs
for the first time.
They're actually writing and creating their
own OKRs for the first time.
And so that's sort of the bottom up process
that we are now repeating in usually like 60
day cycles.
So they basically go through the same
prompt.
Again, a lot of it's answered for them, just
like with a company master prompt,
because AI knows them very well due to
their role master prompt.
And so they then answer those questions.
It creates their clarity board.
It finds opportunities for AI enablement,
whether that's actual creation of
automation or whether that's creation of
prompts.
It then gets people to create and outline
those opportunities themselves and build
them.
And that kind of cycle, then we use stage
three and it's accountability side to kind of
follow up on all of those OKRs and
opportunities over time.
And so that kind of, that bottom up
approach, I'm pretty weak at like following
up with people individually.
It's just not my strength.
So having AI to follow up with people and
also having AI to bottoms up support them
in identifying OKRs,
is really, really helpful.
And then also, part of the Clarity Board
also identifies what people are doing and
whether that surfaces a lot of things.
Sometimes it surfaces a lot of
conversations.
Sometimes it's like people are doing a lot of
busy work and appearing busy, but the
work might not be the right thing.
Sometimes it surfaces that people are
super overutilized, sometimes
underutilized.
That was a long answer.
I'm not sure if that was your question.
That was great because it sounds like you
haven't bothered wasting time asking
questions without having them use Quad.
Yep.
Because, you know, there's a scenario
where the people have not bought in to
any of this.
They're leery of it.
And so it's like, well, I can get this started
by collecting some information and
running it for them.
And then that gets the ball rolling.
So.
The underlying formula is the same in the
sense that you are using the idea of like
building up context persistently.
Right.
And then having Claude interview the
employee and greatly help their ability to
answer those questions and uncover
insights through the use of the master
prompt or the role master prompt in this
case.
And then those conversations produce
multiple outputs, right?
So there's processing on the inputs, right?
Multiple processing on the inputs that
create multiple outputs that are useful to
the organization, right?
So that could be, and one of the companies
I'm training right now, they're at the stage
where we're like finding divergences from
everything from the bottom up we've
uncovered and their actual top-down core
processes, their company master prompt,
et cetera.
So in that example, it's a single prompt
that's literally going through like
40 documents from a single department
and then spitting out multiple outputs.
So it's the same underlying concept, which
is how I've learned to work with AI.
you invite employees to criticize or to say
what isn't working for them or what they
see as opportunities?
Oh, 100%.
That's a big part of it.
could add something there, Don, because
somehow you mentioned, or maybe I
watched the clarity board thing.
And next time I can give a report, because I
got inspired to do this at one of our school
sites where we have about four different
people working in reception.
And I got Claude to give me a draft of how I
could do that.
And it started out with a form.
And then I said, well, couldn't I do it?
Because I'm using Claude sometimes on
the phone, and then it's really helpful just
to talk to it.
And so now we got a whole list, and then I
passed it by the management, and we
added different questions, all that, like,
What don't you like?
And what else could we help you?
And so tomorrow we're going in the Claude
team.
We made a special project inside of that
location's Claude team.
And then everybody's going to get there.
It said to put it in as a project document.
And then you just have to open one version
on the one phone that says run Beatrice's
question thing.
And then they're going to just talk the
answers.
And then we get the manager there to say
what she thinks everybody's supposed to
be doing.
And now I didn't realize that that should
build up.
I know what I was going to do with what I
get at the end, but it's way more than I
would have before.
that's awesome.
So I think that's a great idea, especially for
people who are less computer comfortable,
is to use voice agents.
The only thing I'd say is think about what
are all of the outputs?
And even prompt Claude with this, right?
Here's all the inputs that I'm going to be
getting.
based on these conversations, or here's the
prompt, based on the inputs that you see
I'm going to be getting, give me lots of
ideas for like potentially useful outputs,
right?
Whether they're HTML artifacts, whether
they're, you know, whatever it is, an app,
right?
Reporting, right?
And see what it gives you.
And then basically, you know, you have
your outputs based on that.
And then- I was gonna say, I speak English
better than I speak Portuguese, which is
what people speak here.
And so I got all this stuff first in English and
then you just say, okay, now give me
everything in Portuguese.
And then you got the whole thing in
Portuguese.
So another interesting step is once you get
a list of those outputs, you can then ask
Claude, okay, based on now having all of
this
right?
How can I upgrade my business brain?
Right.
And how can that, you know, help the
entire organization and it'll give you more
ideas and you can like play with it.
Go ahead, Janice.
I'm not 100% sure if I understood you all
correctly.
So what I'm wondering is a little bit, how do
I practically basically work with my team
using cloud or any AI, but basically in this
context, cloud?
Do I have a team's account and make them
all share in one project and open up their
chats so we all see and you have to have a
culture of transparency and that has to
probably be one of the core values.
Otherwise, people are not willing to share
openly.
where how do you actually then work and
share chat's information, feedback, et
cetera, in AI or through AI or with AI?
So two ways you can do it right now.
You can do it through a Cloud project,
which is your master prompt project.
And before you share your master
prompts, which your master prompt's
pretty much done now.
I think you have one more session this
Friday, which we'll add to it.
But you can basically chat with Cloud and
say, hey,
What elements of this master prompt
might be private that I only want
leadership to see or I only want ownership
to see?
And it'll go over it and maybe it'll say, hey,
everyone's wages are in here, right?
Or important financial data is in here.
And then you just say, okay, remove that.
Create a separate version, right?
Remove that information.
And we're going to call this like the full
team master prompt.
And you make a project with that and then
share that project so that they can't see
those those pieces.
So that's one way with Claude.
The other way is use stage three, same
thing, right?
You can have multiple master prompts.
Either way works.
And then when you actually introduce it,
you basically show them, right?
I would do a team training, right?
Get everyone together, show them how to
like start a chat with the master prompt.
And then usually I would take people
through something that gives a very quick
win.
for them, right?
Whatever that is in your situation.
And just show them the example, show
them the benefit of like the extra context
that they get with the master prompt.
And so how does it loop back then,
whatever they type, whatever they chat
with?
I mean, it's not that I want to do crazy
surveillance and want to know everything,
but I think it makes sense to somehow feed
it back, right?
And then have a conversation going rather
than just one direction.
I guess.
Yeah.
So, so with Claude, you won't really know
anything outside of their usage.
And by usage, I literally mean like
percentage max usage.
And you won't have the ability to really
have them create updates to your master
prompt.
So typically if you're doing this with Claude,
you'll have one person, most likely you to
start will be like the admin and you'll be
the person who's like maintaining the
master prompt in Claude.
which is a bit of a pain.
In stage three, there is an ability, which I'll
teach, which is how to change the master
prompt through the chat, which you can't
do in Cloud.
And so it's just like a slash master prompt
update.
And it lets you make changes.
And then your team, so there's a team
owner and there's admins and there's team
members.
And team members can also use that And
then it creates a master prompt edit
request for the owner to approve.
And then, and so, yeah, yeah.
So that's the, again, it's a challenge we've
solved with stage three.
Technically, if you use something your own
and you want it to surveil, you could, we
don't do that.
Yeah.
That's not the idea.
I was wondering more how, how the, just
the feedback gets back, you know, and
Nancy was describing such a conversation
type with a lot of people.
So.
Yeah.
The way, again, with teams, the company
master prompt gets up to date with this
sort of approval system within stage three.
And then the role master prompt has a
separate section within stage three called
my role master prompt for each team
member, and they add to it.
And so that increases the AI's knowledge of
just them personally.
And you can actually see in stage three,
you can see how many knowledge
documents each person on the team has,
right?
Awesome.
I'm going to add one thing
I had asked Claude, like, what do I do now
that I'm going to create this special, you
know, extra, the name of the place is
Lobito.
So they're going to have their own project
mass, and then they're going to have the
data.
And it said, well, after it does whatever it
is, we wanted the outputs to ask that to
make it into a document that I can then
put into my master prompt as a summary
of what that
Sounded reasonable.
So maybe this is useful to see.
Great, Pablo, I'll get to you in a second.
So this is like the role master prompt.
So an admin in an organization can see all
of the people and their teams and how
they're using it.
And then how many files they have within
their role master prompt.
Because as they work with it, there's a
whole curriculum that adds to it.
And so then you can go through and you
can actually see each of the files, download
them, look at them, prompt with them.
You can actually add them to processes
here.
Some of these are in German.
But they create these files in Cloud,
basically, and then upload them to stage
three to have the content.
Yeah, that's how they did it in this team's
curriculum.
But you can also do it within the chat here.
Oh, good.
Yeah, so one of the things I'm doing now is
adding curriculum from within stage three,
and then like a chat within the curriculum
so that you don't have to do the whole sort
of copy from Cloud, download, add to stage
three.
Exactly, yeah.
Cool, thanks.
Go ahead, Bob.
Go ahead, Pavel.
Hello.
I have a question.
I was trying to use your example of clarity
board.
It's working very well.
And I use it not in the HTML.
I try to make it in Excel because it's much
more easy to make changes if I want to in
the future.
Yep.
And I'm wondering maybe you have some
idea about your workflow hub to get
interview from the bottom, from each
employee.
I was thinking about get new iPhone and
open my account with cloud and give
someone maybe to make an interview one
hour.
Maybe you have some solution about this.
Sorry, when you say give them an iPhone,
you mean, can you expand on that?
Give iPhone open cloud and launch this
prompt for clarity board.
So similar to what Nancy is doing with her
school.
Yeah, I think that's great.
Yeah.
I can, if you want, I can give you the prompt
I use for that clarity board.
Um, We want all the prompts.
Because I use your example that you sent
by email, and I ask Cloud to make the same
for me.
Oh, nice.
Yeah, just backwards.
We want your prompt anyway.
Okay.
Result was amazing.
Oh, sorry, Pablo.
Yeah, I have more questions.
And second one that I tried to change
motivation.
So I tried to make a new motivation for
finances, for sales department.
It worked amazing because they create
new KPI dashboard.
I can share my screen if you want.
Just second.
You see?
Uh, each department have, uh, different
KPIs from strategic session, many
initiatives and, uh, one dashboard of all
departments, uh, cloud make it, uh, five
minutes.
It was amazing.
Very fast.
Very cool.
And, uh, just second.
And another question I have.
One color is a different person down below
the different sections.
Different departments.
Yes.
Another question I have.
Do I have to write something in instruction
master prompt instruction?
Sorry, I don't understand.
is set project instruction.
Do you have to write this?
No, you don't have to.
It can be empty?
It can be empty.
Project instructions are pretty similar to
just the project knowledge, which you have
quite full here on the right side there.
So no, you don't have to put anything in
there.
Another question.
Can you show the workflow?
I struggle with this stage three, how to save
new SOP, use RACI and update and share.
Just a second, I share my screen on this
question.
This is what I see.
And I put here this SOP and I see here is
category of blueprints.
I press here and put here guide 1.3
blueprint.
Yep.
Because I don't know how to feel.
We're asking cloud how to make it right.
I don't know.
So what's the question?
That looks good.
The blueprint has an active SOP.
If you want it.
Maybe in the future it will be in next
session how you use the stage three.
Yeah, that's the plan.
Not next session.
I think the one after that is a bit more of
a...
a primer.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah.
So if you share, there's a share button.
So if you share it, yeah, right there, you can
share that with other people in your team
and the way the sharing is nested.
So right now you would be sharing your
core process, which would then share all of
the blueprints and all of the guides.
However, if you go to a blueprint itself, so if
you close this and then click on the SOP,
for the category blueprint.
So that's the core process.
Yeah, the category blueprint was the one
you had open before.
Yeah, and so if you click share there, that
will only share the blueprint and the guides
underneath it.
And then if you go to an individual guide,
it'll only
the guide.
It won't share anything above it
hierarchically.
And how to use this AI tool to update?
Yeah, so generally speaking, you should hit
a new session.
So the plus in the top right.
And then basically, if you go to context
next to the chat, you can add additional
context for all of the underlying and sister
SOPs.
That will only add context if you have a
current SOP.
It's not going to get context from drafts.
Only current.
What's missing right now is your master
prompt is not current.
So if you go to
AI master prompts on the menu under
administration on the left menu.
Yeah, under team settings, AI master
problem.
So you don't have, yeah, so you need a
master prompt in here and you need to set
it as active and setting it as current.
And then you'll have a little toggle in your
chat underneath, which allows you to
choose which master prompts you're using
when you're chatting with the bot.
And so basically that combined with the
role master prompts, which you haven't
learned yet, But basically the role master
prompt plus your company master prompt
is what you chat with AI for.
And it knows about you and your company.
And so if you imagine your individual team
members would also be using that and
they would have and build their own role
master prompt.
And so then when you chat, it knows
significantly more about you and what you
do.
But yeah, if you were where you were,
basically in the AI chat, you just want to
make sure you have your master prompt
on.
You just say, build a new version of this
of this guy.
Right.
And you've given it the context or, you
know, ask me, ask me three questions and
then build a new version of this guy.
And just like Claude, but faster, it'll do that.
And then it'll actually populate it as a, as a
new draft.
And if you go to, you can do things in batch.
So you can say, Hey, build all of the guides
under this blueprint, you know, ask me
four questions.
Right.
And it'll just go and do that and populate it
for you.
So that's a little faster than going to Claude
and chatting and giving it context and
copying and pasting it back in.
Interesting.
Hayden, related to use of Stage 3, I think I
understood you last office hours to say
that you used Google Doc or Drive as a
go-between cloud.
So you didn't try to keep versions in sync.
And I didn't quite follow how you do that
because I didn't see any integration
between Drive and Stage 3.
No.
So there isn't natively an integration.
You have to create a custom script to do
that, which isn't too difficult to do, but you
need to give permissions to basically G
Suite in order to do that.
But what it does for you is it's to give you
the integration between stage three and
Claude.
So Claude uses the Google Docs as sources
instead of .md files.
And then stage three, there's a custom
script that basically says, make with each
of my knowledge documents, update these
Google drive files on a cron job basis.
Right.
Or on a edit by edit basis, whichever way
you want, which basically says, okay, now
Claude stays up to date, which is a real
problem.
So yeah, it's, it's just a Google script.
I need to, I haven't tried like distributing it
to organizations.
So I'm going to talk to my developer, just
make sure that like it's safe and
everything.
Yeah.
and scalable before I send it out.
But that's the idea.
And again, you could, honestly, you can go
back and forth with Claude on how do I do
that?
So.
Okay.
I just didn't quite understand what you
were doing.
So that helps.
Speaking of prompts, I'm not sure if I just
missed it or I'm not sure what the, if we
were supposed to create role prompts
ourselves because they're not included in
the prompts that we were given, right?
We're just creating them ourselves.
Yeah, I kind of got ahead of myself there
because I've been teaching this in the
Teams program.
And so in office hours, people naturally
have questions and I kind of talk about it.
So yeah, we haven't taught it yet.
My goal with stage three is to just add all
the curriculum from Teams in there as well
over time.
And so I think we'll be able to add the first,
I'm hoping, aiming to add the first nine
sessions from Teams into stage three, like
in the next couple of weeks.
And so you could probably just bring it out
to your team.
Um, that way.
But yeah, the concept there again is same
idea.
You are building out a role master prompt
for your team members that really digs
into all of the processes that they touch
and what good looks like in their function,
right?
Whereas you guys have learned in a
broader way what good looks like or great
looks like across various functions and sort
of broader strokes of like a core process.
are going to look like what great looks like
very specifically in their function, right?
Which AI will help teach them and then
teach them to build sort of bottoms up,
um, usually guides and blueprints.
Um, and so they typically do that in the
first three sessions while learning the
fundamentals, right?
The fundamentals are still sort of things
like, you know, three layers of processes,
four layers of SOPs.
Um, what is customers, what is the
customer life cycle etc and then that leads
into the clarity board session.
The clarity procession leads into
opportunity analysis for AI assistance and
like teaching prompts, which then leads
into them, AI actually helping them build
out various prompts that help them as well
as various workflows.
I didn't, you know, Mike, I just asked, I
described the role.
It's okay, the receptionist and that they
have to deal with clients, they have to take
the bills.
And then it just generated quite a good list
and in different categories for me.
And then I passed it around and got people
to just add a few more things and seems
pretty darn good based on the just
describing what a little bit of what they did.
We have another moment.
I'll take advantage of you, Hayden.
I know that you have been involved in
some construction companies, and a lot of
times you'll come into them and discover
they're using QuickBooks, spreadsheets,
and Outlook.
And I just imagine by now, you know, after
you've tried everything on the planet, you
have some favorites about where you'd like
to see the companies running on.
on whatever platforms.
So are you using any CAM platforms that
you really like or do you make all your
own?
What type of construction?
We're doing structural concrete and
retaining walls, that sort of thing.
When I buy a company, you're absolutely
right.
Actually, I usually stick with QuickBooks
Online, by the way.
That's actually part of my stack.
We used to use Procore on some of our
companies.
I'm sure you've looked into this, but there
are AI estimation tools for just about every
single subcontractor construction
company, and some of them are good.
So we do that with plumbing quite
effectively.
What typically ends up happening is the, so
the estimation side of the business is high,
like has a pretty high cost collapse, right?
In most businesses.
And I would say like, that's the piece if
there isn't already a good sub out there
that I'll usually build.
And it's not particularly difficult to build.
And usually I actually will start by building
spreadsheets because everyone knows
how to use spreadsheets.
The project.
So what do you use for project
management?
Chaos.
Okay.
I'm not familiar with that.
There's a whiteboard on the wall.
There's people.
It's makes me very uncomfortable.
And then.
Then there's these spreadsheets with some
different colors on them.
And there's a guy in the back yelling, you
know, so that's pretty.
So.
Yeah.
So project management, again, I would
actually look at using lightweight, easy to
use tools like notion or air table and
building it out with AI in mind versus using
like Microsoft Project or anything super
complex like that, I think that's totally
unnecessary now.
In fact, I think that those two are actually
over their heads and that I'm actually
looking at Smartsheet as something that
they'll find easier to digest because it looks
so much like spreadsheets.
Yeah, so Smartsheet and Airtable are very
similar in that way.
I haven't used a lot of Smartsheet, just not
for any good reason, but I know that
they're big competitors.
Um, yeah.
And I, and I got to take like the other two
are like notion and ClickUp are sort of the
other two that are quite similar.
I've always gone towards ClickUp for
whatever reason.
Um, but yeah, on, on the PM side, like using
that along with like, how do people
communicate, um, online or do that?
Uh, you mean customers or interoffice?
Uh, interoffice.
Uh, they're, they're doing emails and, uh,
conversations really.
Okay.
Um, everybody's in the office, like it's
physically in the office.
Well, you have, you have estimators, you
know, going out and looking at sites and,
and then there, you know, so like the
followup is horrible.
You know, like I see a lot of things falling
through the cracks or potential for things
falling through the cracks.
And so, you know, but buttoning that down
is a high priority.
So from a data perspective, one of the best
things you can do is make sure that every
single communication is recorded.
And so,
So the best way to do that would be just to
say, hey, you know, meetings always have
an agent there or just install something
like, you know, crisp and make sure that
it's running or something.
And that you basically have, whether it's
Slack or Telegram or WhatsApp, you have a
single place that you can have people
communicate online.
And it's not just like texting each other on
cell phones because you can't record that.
But obviously, if you can record everything,
that's actually sort of an advantage of a
remote environment.
It's like everything by nature is recorded.
But if you can record everything, that's
where accountability and reporting can all
get automated for you.
And those two elements will help a lot with
chaos.
So I'd say that step number one is like
figure out from a data perspective, how
can you record your intercompany
communication as much as possible?
And I'll just offer you this.
I've mentioned this before, but this is
Plaud.
And it hooks right on the phone here.
And when you want to record, you ask, is it
going to record this?
Push the button.
It picks up the phone call on both sides.
Oh.
Go to P-L-A-U-D, and it goes on.
It generates, creates a summary, a whole
bunch of lists.
So it's a keeper, you know.
And so I think we should buy these for our
team, our salespeople, estimators, and
then we can capture and understand what
more they need to get their goals
accomplished.
Interesting.
Yeah, that's a fun tool.
I have a feeling that OpenAI's hardware
thing is going to be something like that.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Yeah, for those who didn't hear, it's
P-L-A-U-D.
Right.
I've never used it, but that's awesome.
Do you have other employees using that, or
is it just you right now?
I am the test hamster.
Okay.
Yeah, we use it for phone conversations.
Like, we'd really like to capture everything,
and we use Quo, which used to be open
phone, which is great because you can
have –
Joint texts and communications, it gets
transcripts for the calls.
The problem we run into is my managers
don't want to use it because it runs on
Wi-Fi, so it's not as reliable as cell phone.
So we're running into that issue and really
want to do what Hayden is saying, capture
more of our communications because we
also have some silos of information based
on not capturing calls as much or even
texts that are going to cell phones.
But, like, any solution to that I think helps
tie into this business knowledge really
makes it much more valuable.
Super important.
When we put RingCentral in and discovered
that our person that was taking the
incoming lead calls couldn't care less.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Definitely, yeah.
That was shocking.
RingCentral before we went to Quo, but
just wanted the additional –
communication of quo, but it's not nearly
as big a company as RingCentral.
Yeah.
But having that automated coaching going
on, I can't wait to make it real because
that's going to really make a difference in
the results.
You've been saying this, haven't you,
Hayden?
Yeah, that's the number one workflow I
think everyone needs to input is record all
your conversations, have a workflow that
literally...
transcribes, records in a single place, and
then the workflow actually goes over a
prompt according to that conversation that
then scores the conversation on all sorts of
different things and then ties into your
actual scorecards and reporting, right?
So that you know, if it's a sales
conversation, you know whether it was a
qualified lead or an unqualified lead and
why, right?
And it also scores the salesperson, right?
And flags them for, you know, a low score,
high score,
right, for pipe reviews or call reviews.
I mean, obviously that's from a sales
perspective, but you can do it from an ops
perspective.
You can do it from a leadership
perspective, right, from a training
perspective.
Very, you know, not difficult to do.
The main thing is that first layer of just
capturing all the information and figuring
out the right system for that.
But once you've got that, it's like very easy
and cheap to maintain.
Like you, Don, within three days of
launching this, we identified that one of
our salespeople was selling a competing
product and fired them.
Like this stuff is happening in all of our
businesses, right?
So there's that.
But, you know, you have been down this
path and created all that structure you
were just describing.
And so you've got it to where it's clear to
you.
But to me, it seems like a little bit of
mountain to climb with Claude, you know,
to make it real.
So say more, please.
So I have not done the Claude stuff or any
of the, like, let's say in a construction
company,
with a physical office doing that layer of
data recording.
I personally have not done that.
I've only, in those situations, I've only really
done say, you know, using Podium and
recording everything on that side for like
CSRs, dispatchers, et cetera.
Because I personally have not bought and
integrated a construction business in the
last six months, which went all the way
down.
Yeah.
I mean, I like, like everything I would
describe the problem and ask quad to one,
three, one it.
Right.
So actually I have like a protocol that
you're familiar with the one, three, one.
Yeah.
So for those who don't know, one, three,
one is like you often use it within teams.
I use it with AI.
But one, three, one is when you have a
problem, describe one outcome, three
paths to a solution or three solutions, and
then one recommendation.
And then like the follow on with AI, which
is great, is to say, as part of a 131, identify
the pros and cons of each solution and
then do a second pass of the 131, analyzing
each of the pros and mitigating each of the
risks to come up with three more solutions
and then give me the recommendation.
So there's a nice little prompt for you to
save to your master prompt is like, when
you, when I say one, three, one, do these
two things.
And that's a great way for them to come
back to you.
And with a fairly well thought out version
on how to, how do I accomplish, you know,
the data collection process.
Yeah.
And they, and they build out behind that.
Once you get the data, the, the reports you
were talking about and the feedback.
So some of you just keep asking quad to
develop that stuff for you.
And yep.
And then the tree, the triggers, and then
there's,
There's a, so the data comes in, which is
like a recording, for example, the what's
the connection.
Okay.
So that arrives wherever.
So like let's say you have a transcript,
right?
So you would usually tie it into wherever
you keep your information.
So let's say Google drive, maybe a lot of
small businesses put it there.
They'll put it into a certain Google drive
folder, right?
Both the transcript and the actual
recording.
So people can refer to it.
Then it usually, updates the spreadsheet,
right?
And then one of the steps will be the
prompt, right?
That then updates the spreadsheet based
on whatever you're prompting it to go over
the transcript for, right?
And then you might have a layer of
notification, right?
So you might have a layer of notification
for, hey, you just had this call.
Here's the follow-up.
Here are the notes.
Here's the follow-up along with the next
two emails or texts.
It's all being recorded.
in whatever CRM you put it in, which is
another step.
Do you want me to send these or edit?
And that would usually go out on whatever
you choose to be your intercompany
communication platform, maybe
WhatsApp, maybe Telegram, maybe Slack.
I think Telegram seems to be the free
common solution here.
And then your salesperson just says, yes,
no, change this.
And then it goes, it'll usually have another
thing that triggers after which updates
reporting, right?
So updates reporting to say that the call
was held to say that the call was qualified
or unqualified, or the call was a show or a
no show.
And so, yeah, all of that happens in one
workflow.
Usually the trigger, depending on the type
of call, usually the trigger would be that a
bot attended a call on Google calendar.
So that's usually the trigger.
If you don't, if they're more ad hoc,
and your meetings are ad hoc, you'll have
to have a different trigger.
It might have to be manual.
If it's like literally someone walking into a
room and maybe Plod has its own little
connection where whenever you click the
button, it sends a trigger.
Probably does.
It should.
Yeah.
But you'll have to figure out how to
connect that.
And in that video that you made with
Tiago, when he asked you, there's a bar,
like a CR code, one of those codes there
that gives you a really nice notion, like
description exactly how to build that thing.
Yeah, so that was done in Zapier.
That was done by an employee of our
company who's not a developer.
It's funny, that exact thing, I paid a
developer to develop.
I think it paid them like 40 grand and it
took them like two months, maybe a year
ago.
And we never used it because it didn't work
properly.
And I didn't have my processes like
correctly identify it.
That one, like Andy did in, Andy's in the
Philippines.
Andy did that in maybe 2015.
two weeks total in his spare time.
And I think it costs us maybe like 30 bucks
a month in dApps.
That's the power of AI enabling your team.
Yeah, it's terrific what we can do.
Yeah.
It's really helpful seeing what you, who are
miles ahead of me, are showing us because
that's super important.
I don't even think I'm miles ahead of you.
I think I might be six months ahead of you.
In this day and age, that's a lot, right?
But I'm trying to catch up.
Okay.
4.30 AM club.
I think we have time for another one or
two questions if anyone else wants to, has
anything else to discuss.
I use something like Don says, this
Soundcore.
It's a little different.
Also voice recorder and my workflow is
using Notebook LM and
transcribe conversation and make a Google
sheet and update one Google chip for, for
example, finance meetings and send the
report to my old team.
So what's the trigger on that?
On that, like, do you have to like touch
something?
Yeah.
So little data here.
And so based on your conversation, it
knows which sheet to update and.
which Notebook LM to put it in?
No, it's manually.
I just sent from the phone, sent to
Notebook LM in this notebook and
transcribed by my hands.
Right now it's not automated, it's
manually.
Yeah, I mean, hypothetically, you should be
able to...
Actually, the first workflow I ever created
was maybe two years ago and it was a
voice recorder.
So I just had my voice recorder app, and I
did it on make.com.
And it was literally, I would say, it was a
simple workflow where I would say
something, it would save it to Google Drive,
it would analyze what it was, and then
send it to the right place.
And so, same concept.
That's cool.
I use it every day, four times a day, very
often.
Awesome.
What's that one called?
It's a show.
Spell it for us.
We want to buy one.
What's it called?
This is called sound core work.
Sound core work.
Oh, it's the same company that makes my
headphones.
It's like a magnet.
Right.
Yeah, the magnet is part of mine, too.
So I got the sound, S-O-U-N-D, and was the
last word C-O-R-E?
It's my wife telling me it's Anker.
Soundcore, C-O-R-E.
Is that what you think?
Yep.
The first autocomplete on Google is
Soundcore Work versus Plod.
Okay, perfect.
And there's another called TIC note, T-I-C
note.
Now it's gonna be all over the place, no
place to hide.
Aiden, I have a, if nobody's got another
question, I have a question just related to
trying to store business knowledge and
personal knowledge and capturing that
kind of along the lines of this, but maybe
just small bits of information.
You know, I think historically you had to
look a lot at what the UI was going to be
and how people are going to access
information.
And I was listening to Nate B.
Jones.
I don't know if you follow him, but he was
talking about an open brain and
which is really just using a desktop base
like Supabase and capturing all this
information because it's more machine
readable, more accessible by AI.
And I just wonder if we're thinking as
business owners of capturing knowledge,
are we at a point where pretty soon we can
not pay so much attention to that access
layer, the UI?
Because even Comparative City, and I think
a month ago he used an example with
Obsidian, and then he's saying, well, that's
yesterday.
Today it's relational database.
My experience with RAG systems is that
they are thus far not as accurate as
recording As like discerning important
pieces of context and only recording those
pieces.
So I 100% agree that that is the way we're
going and that's the way we're heading.
RAG is kind of slow and not that effective.
Have you used RAG much?
Like, have you?
No, you know, I'm only, I'm not really
well-versed on what exactly RAG would be.
So when you say RAG,
that's what you would think of when you're
using a relational database without a lot of
structure.
Yeah.
So, so usually like the way they've done it
historically is with like something like pine
cone or a vector database.
Right.
You could, I mean, yeah.
So, so basically the, the issue there is like
actually creating a system that effectively
finds, let's say needle in a haystack style,
knowledge quickly and efficiently and
cheaply is historically has been quite hard
to do.
And in my, my, the way I've been looking at
this as technology progresses, because I've
been comparing rag versus master prompt
versus prompt injection, full prompt
injection and the compounding, like, uh,
the token limits, the token windows
increase, right?
The usable token windows increase, um,
the cost of tokens go down so far faster
than the ability for sort of RAG, in my
opinion, to keep up.
And so as long as that continues to happen,
I will continue using this approach.
In terms of recording absolutely everything
and that like what you actually need to do
is you need a system that intelligently, and
this is what the second brain I think leads
to, right?
I have not built this yet.
So this is hypothetical.
But if you're able to record everything, you
need a second brain orchestrator that
discerns what's worth recording and
adding to your second brain.
I don't think it's everything gets recorded
into a rag database and then you go, like,
that's way too much data, right?
And so it's that discernment piece, which is
like a well-trained master prompt AI
orchestrator that discerns what's
important to be updated.
And that, again, I think for a long time is
going to have a human in the loop
component.
right.
Where it's going to be just messaging you
whenever, you know, on Telegram or
whatever saying, Hey, based on this, I think
this aspect of the master prompt needs to
be updated.
Can I do it?
Right.
Yes.
And so I think everyone's job is going to be
talking to agents on your phone.
Does that answer your question?
So if you were, thinking about setting out
to really gather all your company's
knowledge at this time, considering there's
going to be a lot of changes, just guessing,
like, what's the best way to think about,
like, where would you do that?
Like, you know, I'm used to using Notion to
gather knowledge, but I like the idea of
Obsidian, but maybe not for Teams
because of the way, you know, so I, as a
team, how would you think about
gathering team knowledge?
So I would first think of what is the MISI
framework, right?
The mutually exclusive, cumulatively
exhaustive framework of a knowledge of a
business, which is what Empower is, right?
So what are resources?
What are priorities?
What are processes in the company?
Set that all up, right?
And then how do I extract this data from
the individuals in the company first, right?
And then add it to whatever structure I
have.
So in Cloud Code, I literally have companies
and then every company has resources,
processes, priorities, and I just populate
out the folders.
And if you're more advanced at this, you
have bots interviewing your employees.
Based on what that happens, it populates
and updates throughout.
But I think ultimately the organizational
knowledge is often going to come from
your employees because they hold the
tribal knowledge in a business, especially in
small businesses.
And then maybe secondarily through
integrations with tech, you know, with
your CRM, with your finance data, et
cetera.
But, I mean, I think employees is the hack.
Okay.
I guess I'm thinking about it not so much as
SOPs and guides and company knowledge
that way, but maybe more data that we
might be capturing on a day-to-day basis
regarding clients and, like, you know, You
know, just thinking about that sort of or
specific technical knowledge related to the
work we do, which, of course, some of that
would be captured in guides.
But, yeah, I think that's helpful thinking
about, you know, with stage three and
gathering that data.
I'm thinking kind of the peripheral stuff
that goes on all the time.
I mean, it needs to be, I still look at this as
like customer touch points, right?
Every customer touch point is a source of
data, right?
And so, but that still needs to be in your
processes, right?
Whether that's a layer of automation
workflow, you know, I still look at that as
part of a process.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah, really.
It really is.
How are you capturing that every time?
I always feel that there's a goldmine in the
email history.
To me, that needs to be mined.
I just want to mention that this thing I've
been talking about with Cortex and
Notebook LM, one of the reasons why it got
my attention is I can get a list of all the
sources of all my notebooks.
put them into something else, and I can
sort them out and all that.
So that helps me control what I've been
putting in there and helps me silo it as new
needs arise.
So people are building add-ons, trying to
make Notebook LM more useful.
And is that like a Chrome extension?
Yeah, it is.
And I was writing to Mike about this on the
chat on the curriculum there, on the
whatever you call it, community.
And so you'll find the note in there if you
want to take a look at it.
But the minute I saw it, I bought a lifetime
license for $39.
And it turned out to be better than I
expected.
So I'm kind of raving about that right now.
It'll be short-lived probably.
A notebook will probably –
You know, take all their great ideas and
put them to work.
After your message, I also buy this.
Yeah, it's amazing.
You
goldmine emails.
I would agree.
Do you have any good app technology
which you would let into your archives,
email archives, and then with a certain
context, look through them?
You
that world is changing really fast.
Hayden knows a lot more about this than I
do, I think.
But it appears that even I think Microsoft
themselves are bringing something to the
table on this.
I just thought I saw a headline go by about
that.
But it's like kind of a no-brainer that an
organization, you know, who's got 30
people sending emails around, you know,
all that wealthy value of information ought
to be getting –
absorbed into the Borg.
How are you doing it, Don, on the email
side?
Luckily, I'm using Gmail in a workspace,
and I use little add-ons that let me export,
let me gather a bunch of emails and turn
them into a PDF.
It's really stupid, but it has been useful
even in my little world here, you know, but
I'll And then, of course, Gemini pretends to
read my email account.
But that's horrible.
I find that to be, you know, fails all the
time.
But Claude, I find Claude, I hooked Claude
up with my whole workspace.
And I'm finding Claude to be much better
than Gemini on terms of interrogating
what's in the email.
And did you do that as just like it's
integrated, like it's personalized?
Basic add-on?
Are you using an MCP?
I just connected Cloud to my workspace
and gave it access to my spreadsheets and
the docs.
Go ahead.
Take everything.
My life's not that interesting.
kind of like you, Don.
I've been waiting for Gmail to do this
properly.
I didn't think it was worth my time because
I assumed that by now they would have
done it.
So I'm not actually doing it, and I'm not
willing to give OpenClaw access to my
email.
So yeah, I can't offer a lot of advice here.
Is anyone else using AI to mine their email
actively?
I was trying to do this, but I was scared
about this.
Yeah, I feel the same.
would be a great help because actually we
are trying to create for our leasers a kind of
a single source of truth.
And it's coming from from several sources.
And one of them is huge.
And it will be going back for basically the
past years, I guess, could be email.
So if anybody has an idea how we could do
that, that would be really, really helpful for
us.
I
mention that there's an outfit called Mail
Suite.
They're busy building add-ons that hook
onto Gmail.
I don't know what else they do, but they're
constantly innovating ways to extract more
value out of the emails.
That's the one I've been using on my own
Gmail account.
Unfortunately, I mean, it's kind of sad that
that's the best we have right now.
But it's still, you know, they're creating
these little widgets, really, and it's like, oh,
here's one that'll do this, that'll do that,
you know?
So it's just little add-ons for the time being.
There's got to be a nice Cloud Code
integration here.
Ultimately, what you want to do is export
your entire Gmail database.
And as soon as you can do that, then you
can tear it to shreds, extract what's in
there.
gonna look into this.
This is...
Thanks Hayden.
Yep.
Can I show you one more workflow?
Go for it.
I'll share my screen.
I create, uh, with cloud, uh, one project, uh,
like, um, strategic assistant.
And, uh, before I use a classic hosting
country and cloud gave me this format.
This is, uh, drivers initiatives.
Each driver has some initiatives,
departments, and, uh, they update backlog
in work or done.
Finish.
And I upload this SCV file put in this chat in
cloud.
This SCV file.
It analyze changes, how many initiatives,
what is changed, and give me feedback.
And I ready to go make this session with
my It's a very cool improvement.
And then I create one more chart.
Put here everything that we speak in this
session.
It analyzes key points, questions.
And give me feedback.
I check this feedback and say, okay, I agree
with you.
This is very good.
And it gives me preparation for next
session.
So in one moment, I'm ready to next
It's amazing.
With cloud, I make this strategic session
and update very fast and visual how many
we finished initiatives, what was in
progress and in backlog and how we move
it.
on this second mouse.
One thing we're implementing right now
for similar, for like initiative, for strategic
initiatives, we use that like the OKR,
objective and key results framework.
But basically in stage three, we have like
agent, like routine agents, which are
basically cron jobs, right?
Which allow you to actually follow up with
a task in an AI chat for each team member.
based on their initiative, and then apply a
prompt to it.
And so if you wanted to use something like
Hoshi Konri as a framework, you would just
apply the Hoshi Konri side of the prompt to
it.
But this way, it could then kick off on a
schedule, like a time schedule, updates for
all initiatives.
And then based on interviewing back and
forth with your team members, then
update a sheet like this live.
which for me, again, one of the things I
think is going to be really interesting with
AI is all your employees will have probably
multiple objectives or initiatives going on
at a time that they never would have had
before because you just didn't have the
capacity to delegate and ask them to do
that.
This is super cool.
And every department have their own
dashboard.
this is initiatives like project and subtask.
And we have small gantt chart and they
track it and make update.
And I give them all access to all initiatives.
And after maybe one, two, three, five
months, they forget about this.
What was it about?
And I give them access to notebook lm and
they can go and ask questions here, some
question and remind
what was one year ago, what was it about?
It's very good because everyone forget
after five months.
Very cool.
timely for something I'm working on too.
I may follow up and ask.
you to share a couple of things if that's
okay.
Cool.
Well, thank you, everyone.
I'll see you on Friday.
Thank you.
I'll be presenting the remainder of the
sessions.
Yep.
See you Friday
1 p.m.
Eastern.
Take care, everyone.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
Bye.